Guide to the Elizabeth Burtner papers, 1903-2003 MS2150
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Elizabeth Burtner papers
1903-2003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2150
10.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains programs, brochures, clippings, scripts, sketches, notes, correspondence, press releases, scores, research materials, biographies, and photographs dating from 1903-2003 and was collected by Elizabeth Burtner in the course of her career as professor of dance at The George Washington University.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated by Elizabeth Burtner in 2006.
Historical or Biographical Note
Elizabeth Burtner (1906-2009) was a professor of dance at The George Washington University. She is credited with introducing modern dance into the curriculum, increasing dance performances, and organizing more dance groups. Burtner graduated from Hood College in 1927 with a bachelor's degree in Dance, and received a master's degree from Columbia University in 1935. She studied at Bennington College, New York University, with the Humphrey Weidman Group, the Martha Graham School, and other New York Studios. She preformed with the Evelyn Davis Dance Ensemble in Washington, D.C. She joined the faculty of GW in 1938 as a dance instructor and archery coach in the Physical Education Department.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains programs, brochures, clippings, scripts, sketches, notes, correspondence, press releases, scores, research materials, biographies, and photographs. The material dates from 1903-2003, and was collected by Elizabeth Burtner in the course of her career as professor of dance at The George Washington University. The collection contains both materials relating specifically to GW's dance program, and materials relating to trends in dance and prominent dancers.
Collection Organization
Organized into two series: Dance program at The George Washington University and Dancers and trends in dance.
Dance; Washington (D.C.); Modern dance; Photographs; Dancers; George Washington University; Burtner, Elizabeth
- Dance program at The George Washington University, 1938-1995; MS2150 Series 1; 3 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains materials related to Burtner's work as a professor of dance at The George Washington University. Most of the materials, including programs, clippings, scripts, sketches, notes, correspondence, press releases, scores, research materials, photographs, were arranged by Burtner into albums by topic. Burtner's arrangement has been preserved. Photographs have been placed in separate folders directly behind the materials with which they were originally filed. The bulk of the series consists of materials related to performances given by Orchesis and Dance Production Groups. These materials are arranged by the performance (e.g., Annual Spring Concert, Carnival, Homecoming, etc.). Schedules, budgets, programs, correspondence, and memoranda relating to the administration of Orchesis and Dance Production Groups are included as well. This series also contains materials, such as clipping, programs, and correspondence, related to noteworthy dance students and their careers subsequent to their study at The George Washington University.
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert, 1938-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Orchesis, 1935 ca. --1945 ca. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Text on photograph: "Orchesis--late 1930's--early 1940's Technique, study??"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Orchesis, 1940 ca. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    "Orchesis: Jerry Ross, Lucy Petta, and ? 1940"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Orchesis, 1940 ca. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    "Orchesis: Lucy Petta and Jerry Ross 1940"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Jerry Ross, 1940 ca. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Jerry Ross, 1940 ca. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Text on photograph: "Jerry Ross GWU (Orchesis / Dance Production Groups) Dance Technique circa 1940"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Jerry Ross, 1940 ca. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Text on photograph: "Jerry Ross Orchesis circa 1940 (later named Dance Production Groups) G.W. University"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Elizabeth Burtner, 1940 ca. --1949 ca. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Text on photograph: "Elizabeth Burtner 1940's (date of photo) Head of GW University Dance Program, Fall 1937-Spring 1972; Director of Dance Production Groups Fall 1937-Spring 1970"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Recreation Hall and Dance Studio, 1940 ca. --1949 ca. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Text on photograph: "Recreation Hall, and the dance studio, The George Washington University."
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Bolero, 03/19/1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Text on photograph: "From: BOLERO Lucie Petta - Jerry Rosey (later Jerry Ross) (March 19, 1940)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Saluation, 03/28/1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Text on photograph: "From: SALUATION Elizabeth Burtner (1948)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Saluation, 03/28/1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Text on photograph: "From: SALUATION Elizabeth Burtner - Jerry Ross (formerly Jerry Rosey) (Friday, March 28, 1941)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Saluation, 03/28/1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Text on photograph: "From: SALUATION Elizabeth Burtner - Jerry Ross (formerly Rosey) March 28, 1941"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--America is Big with Enterprise, 03/18/1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Text on photograph: "From: AMERICA IS BIG WITH ENTERPRISE (Theme and Variations) Jane Burroughs Thomson, Joan Giles, Suzanne Dunning, Nancy Marmer 3/18/42"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Witchcraft, 04/12/1945 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Text on photograph: "Witchcraft (concert April 12, 1946 Lisner Aud.) Elizabeth Burtner and Orchesis I"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Witchcraft, 04/12/1945 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Text on photograph: "Witchcraft (concert April 12, 1946 [sic], Lisner Aud.) Elizabeth Burtner and Orchesis I"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Witchcraft, 04/12/1945 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Text on photograph: "WITCHCRAFT 4/12/45 E. Burtner, Choreographer, Costumes, The Accused"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Text on photograph: "Tom Pence DPG 1947-54 GWU, Louise Whiting DPG 1946-51 GWU"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Text on photograph: "Tom Pence Louise Whiting From: THREE SISTERS 1947"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Text on photograph: "From: THREE SISTERS (1948)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Text on photograph: "From: THREE SISTERS Katherine Killeen and Phyllis Sheppy premiered 1947"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Text on photograph: "From: THREE SISTERS Phyllis Sheppy and Katherine Killeen (1948)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Text on photograph: "THREE SISTERS (from left - Phyllis Sheppy, Tom Pence, Katherine Killeen and Louise Whiting - 1948)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Three Sisters, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Katherine Killeen, 1948 ca. --1950 ca. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Text on photograph: "Katherine Killeen Orchesis 1948-1950s"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Pastoral, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Text on photograph: "From: PASTORAL Louise Whiting and Tom Pence (1949)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Pastoral, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Pastoral, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Text on photograph: "From: PASTORAL Louise Whiting and Tom Pence 1949"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Patterns, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    PATTERNS: Phyllis Sheppy (dance major) 1949
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Return, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Text on photograph: "From: THE RETURN Elizabeth [name deleted] and Tom Walker (1949)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Holiday Mood, 03/08/1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Text on photograph: "HOLIDAY MOOD 3/8/49 Tom Pence, Louise Whiting (far right)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Holiday Mood, 03/08/1949 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Text on photograph: "HOLIDAY MOOD 3/8/49 Tom Pence, Louise Whiting (far right, down/upstage)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Holiday Mood, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Text on photograph: "George Washington University--Students Phyllis Sheppy, daughter of Mrs. Mary H. Sheppy of 3109 Mt. Pleasant st. nw and Tom Pence son of Mrs. Susie Pence, of 4108 21st Rd. North, Arlington, Va. from a scene in Holiday Mood, one of the dance to be given by the Dance Production Groups of The George Washington University in a modern dance concert, Friday, March 18, 8:30 p.m., Lisner Auditorium, 21st and H sts. nw."
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Women's dressing room, 03/18/1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Text on photograph: "GWU Dance Production Groups Dance Concert, March 18, 1949 Women's Dressing Room (3 flights up), Back Stage, Lisner Auditorium. Louise Whiting (on stool), Julia Halloran (costume designer), Phyllis Sheppy, Lorna Burdsall"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Unknown production, 1950 ca. --1959 ca. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Text on photograph: "Lillemar Spitzer Steven Luke the '50s"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Unknown production, 1950 ca. --1959 ca. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Text on photograph: "the '50s Sarah Horsburgh stage R, later married Bill (William Cain), made the Roxetts [sic] NY City"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Tom Pence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Text on photograph: "FOR RELEASE SUNDAY, MARCH 12, 1950 Tom Pence, son of Mrs. Susie Pence, of 4108 North 21st Rd., North, Arlington, Va. Pence will dance in the concert to be given by the George Washington University Dance Production Groups Friday, March 17, at 8:30 p.m. in Lisner Auditorium, 21st and H sts."
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--On stage before the show begins, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--On stage before the show begins, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Aerialists, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    "From: THE AERIALISTS Margaret Clausen - Tom Pence 3/17/1950"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Aerialists, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Text on photograph: "From: THE AERIALISTS Lorna Burdsall - Richard Peppers - Margaret Clausen - Tom Pence - Louise Whiting - Richard Hildreath Friday, March 17, 1950"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Aerialists, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Aerialists, 1950 (Flat box 8, Folder 1)
    Sketch of costume for The Aerialists, signed Don Kline. Text on reverse: "From: THE AERIALIST Margaret Clausen and Tom Pence. Choreography, E. Burtner. 3/17/50 DPG (Dance Production Groups) Costumes: Don Kline, Head of Art Department."
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN Claudia Chapline, Tom Pence, Margaret Clausen (March 17, 1950) From The George Washington University Alumni Review, June 1951"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Pastoral, 03/17/1950 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Text on photograph: "From: PASTORAL Louise Whiting and Tom Pence taking bows at concert 3/17/50 Virginia Csonka accompanist at the piano (also composer)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert, 1951-1959 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ballads, 02/13/1951 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Text on photograph: "From: BALLAD SUITE what shall we do with The Drunken Sailor Don Dilley Carl Anderson John Wo[j]t[owicz] Ed Lum"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ballads, 02/13/1951 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Text on photograph: "From: BALLADS The Drunken Sailor Edwin Lum etc. (Feb. 13, 1951)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Comments on Spring, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Text on photograph: "From: COMMENTS ON SPRING Louise Whiting Schmidt and Tom Pence 2/23/51"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Mother and Two Eligible Daughters, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    "From: MOTHER AND TWO ELIGIBLE DAUGHTERS Sarah Horsburgh, Tom Pence, Patricia Weaver, Betty Silverman Friday 23, 1951"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    "From: MEN AND WOMEN Tom Pence, WIlliam Cain, Sarah Horsburgh, Joan Higginson 2/23/51"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN 2/23/51 Tom Pence Joan Higginson Sarah Horsburgh William Cain"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN Claudia Chapline and Margaret Clausen 2/23/51"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN 2/23/51 William Cain Margaret Clausen"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Mutt and Jeff, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Text on photograph: "From: MUTT AND JEFF 2/23/51 Sarah Horsburgh - Mrs. Mutt's Mother; Joan Higginson - Mrs. Mutt; Edwin Lum - Jeff; William Cain - Mutt
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Mutt and Jeff, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Text on photograph: "From: MUTT AND JEFF Edwin Lum - Jeff; Claudia Chapline - The Girl Who Tries Hard"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Mutt and Jeff, 02/23/1951 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Text on photograph: "From: MUTT AND JEFF 2/23/51 Sarah Horsburgh, Mrs. Mutt's mother; Joan Higginson, Mrs. Mutt; Edwin Lum, Jeff; WIlliam Cain, Mutt"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 03/12/1951 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN 3/12/51 Claudia Chapline Tom Pence"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Theme and Variations, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Text on photograph: "THEME AND VARIATIONS Lola Gernova Milica Hasalova, Margaret Psaltis"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Witchcraft, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Text on photograph: "From SALEM WITCHCRAFT Joan Higginson, the Accused William Cain, the Minister"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Witchcraft, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Text on photographs: "WITCHCRAFT 1945 premiered"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The American Girl: Flapper, 03/13/1953-03/14/1953 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Text on photograph: "From the Suite, THE AMERICAN GIRL: FLAPPER Sarah Horsburgh - William Cain and Group II (March 13 and 14, '53)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Honky Tonk Blues, 03/1953 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Text on photograph: "William Cain and Sarah Horsburgh in Honky Tonk Blues - March 1953"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Military Ball, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Text on photograph: "MILITARY BALL Lola Gernova and Tom Pence (1954)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/12/1954-03/13/1954 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/12/1954-03/13/1954 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/12/1954-03/13/1954 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/12/1954-03/13/1954 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Abstraction, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Facades, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    "From: FACADES Jumbo Charlotte Mickelson March 25/26, 1955"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Facades, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    Text on photograph: "Dance Production Groups G.W.U. FACADES Sir Beelzebub 1955"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Facades, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Text on photograph: "D. P. Groups GWU FACADES Sir Beelzebub 1955" "Charlotte Mickelson, Barbara Brisker, Verlyn Brown, Loydell Jones, Kitty Lee Landess"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Facades, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Text on photograph: "FACADES 3/25/26/55 Kitty Lee Landess and Chalotte Mickelson"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Facades, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Text on photograph: "FACADES 3/25,26/55 Charlotte Mickelson (seated)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    Text on photograph: "From: THE QUEEN'S CONSCIENCE Milica Hasalova 3/25,26/1955 premiered 1954"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Crazy Pants and Pony Tails, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    Text on photograph: "CRAZY PANTS AND PONY TAILS Lillemor Spitzer, Tom Pence, George Mazor D.P. Groups, G.W.U. March 25, 26 '55"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Folk Piece, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    "From: FOLK PIECE Lillemor Spitzer and Tom Pence March 25 and 26, 1955"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Folk Piece, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Folk Piece, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Geraldine, The Ballerina, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    Text on photograph: "From: GERALDINE, THE BALLERINA Verlyn Brown and George Mozer March 25 and 26, 1955"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Geraldine, The Ballerina, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    Text on photograph: "From: GERALDINE, THE BALLERINA Geraldine - Verlyn Brown, Sam - George Mozer DPG Concert 3/25,26/55"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN Duo Lillemor Spitzer and George Mozer 3/25,26/55 premiered 3/23/51"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Men and Women, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    Text on photograph: "From: MEN AND WOMEN Duo Lillemor Spitzer and George Mozer 3/15/26/55 premiered 2/23/51 [sic]"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    Text on photograph: "From: THE QUEEN'S CONSCIENCE Milica Hasalova 3/25,26/55 premiered 1954"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--The Queen's Conscience, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    Text on photograph: "From: THE QUEEN'S CONSCIENCE Duo Lillemar Spitzer Milica Hasalova 3/25,26/55 premiered 1954"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ziccary Zeven, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    "From ZICCARY ZEVEN Lenore Alexander 3/25,26/55"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ziccary Zeven, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ziccary Zeven, 03/25/1955-03/26/1955 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    Text on photograph: "ZICCARY ZEVEN 3/25,26/55"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Modern Fantasy, 03/23/1956-03/24/1956 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    Text on photograph: "From: MODERN FANTASY March 23 and 24, 1956 Milica Hasalova, Gayla April, George Mozer"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Show Piece, 03/23/1956-03/24/1956 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    "From: SHOW PIECE Show Pony, Milica Hasalova, March 23 and 24, 1956 E. Burtner, leader with whip"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Show Piece, 03/23/1956-03/24/1956 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Stranger from Life, 03/23/1956-03/24/1956 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    Text on photograph: "From: STRANGER FROM LIFE Hetty Mitchell March 23 and 24, 1956"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Stranger from Life, 03/23/1956-03/24/1956 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    "From: STRANGER FROM LIFE Hetty Mitchell 3/23 and 24/56 (premiered 3/17/50)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Caribbean Suite, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Folk Suite, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    "From: FOLK SUITE Lament Elizabeth Appleton March 22, 23 1957"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Madeline, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    Text on photograph: "George Washington University students L to R, Lenore Alexander and Gregg Mayer, portray Madeline and her friend for Ludwig Bemelman's story of the madcap Paris school girl, Madeline, in an original dance sequence created at the university in 1957 entitled 'Madeline and the Bad Hat'."
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Madeline, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    Text on photograph: "George Washington University students Gregg Mayer (foreground) and Lenore Alexander (back) portray Ludwig Bemelman's Madeline and her friend from the students original dance sequence 'Madeline and the Bad Hat' created at the university in 1957."
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Madeline, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    "From: MADELINE March 22 and 23, 1957 Nurse Clavel, Julia Bay"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Madeline, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Madeline, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Madeline, 03/22/1957-03/23/1957 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Broadway Suite: West Side Story, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    Text on photograph: "From: BROADWAY SUITE: WEST SIDE STORY 4/25/26/58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Broadway Suite: West Side Story, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    Text on photograph: "1958 West Side Story"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Broadway Suite: West Side Story, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    Text on photograph: "From: BROADWAY SUITE - WEST SIDE STORY 4/25/26/58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Broadway Suite: West Side Story, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Conversation Piece, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    Text on photograph: "1958 Coversation Piece Arthur Bauman in leap frog"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ace High, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ace High, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Ace High, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    Text on photograph: "ACE HIGH James Black and Jerry Osborne (two gamblers)"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Greensleeves, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Greensleeves, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    Text on photograph: "Greensleeves Gregg Mayer April 25/26 '58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Once a Year Day, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    Text on photograph: "From: ONCE A YEAR DAY Miriam Levitan (in the air) 4/25 and 26/58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Once a Year Day, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    Text on photograph: "PICNIC OR ONCE A YEAR DAY Steve Luke ( R stage) 1958"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Once a Year Day, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    Text on photograph: "PICNIC or ONCE A YEAR DAY Jerry Osborne jumping 1958 concert 4/25 and 26/58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Once a Year Day, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Permutations and Combinations, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Permutations and Combinations, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    Text on photograph: "From: 1958 PERMUTATIONS AND COMBINATIONS Arthur Bauman is center of dancers on the audience stage right"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Song Within, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    "From: SONG WITHIN Facade Gregg Mayer and Jerry Osborne, April 25, 26 '58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Song Within, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Song Within, 04/25/1958-04/26/1958 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    Text on photograph: "From: SONG WITHIN Gregg Mayer and Jerry Osborne April 25 and 26/58"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Americana Hoe Down, 04/24/1959-04/25/1959 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    "From: AMERICANA Hoe Down Linda Claster, Bernard Rapport [sic] and Robine Andrau 4/24,25/59"
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Salem Witchcraft, 04/24/1959-04/25/1959 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Annual Spring Dance Concert--Salem Witchcraft, 04/24/1959-04/25/1959 (Box 1, Folder 129)